Mohamed Sharaf

LinkedIn | GitHub | Facebook

Location: Egypt, Kafr El-Sheikh Email: sazxsazx987987@gmail.com | Mobile: 01020115643

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

I am a highly skilled web developer with over **1** years of experience in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Jquery, AJAX, PHP, MySQL, OOP, PDO, Laravel. I have knowledge of popular frameworks such as Laravel and experience with MVC frameworks.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages : JavaScript, PHP, HTML, CSS

Frameworks : Laravel

Libraries : Bootstrap, Jquery, Ajax, Echarts, Yajra, Laratrust, FullCalendar, Datatables

Databases : MySQL

Dev Tools : Visual Studio Code, Git, GitHub

EXPERIENCE

Freelancing
Dec 2021 – Present

E-MAD
Remote – Kafr El-Sheikh

Designed and developed dynamic and responsive websites using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP, Ajax, Laravel

- Worked with **REST APIs** to retrieve and display data from databases
- Improved website performance and speed through query optimization techniques
- Writing Clean Testable code
- A Mentor for a team working on a Management Platform

Backend TrainingApr 2021 – Dec 2021CreativeoEgypt, El-Mansora

- · Built a website for a resturant using native PHP
- Built a CRM website for a grauduate student

EDUCATION

HIMITBachelor of Management Information System
Kafr-El-Sheikh
2018 – May 2022

PROJECTS

Aisha HTML, CSS, Js, PHP, Laravel, MySQL

Built Dashboard Fully functional Optimized website for **speed and user experience** Added needed features and statistics using charts and a calendar Participated in Database Design and database Structure Built CRUD Module

Resturant HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Git, PHP

A CRUD application Using native PHP

Design of Database Structure

CERTIFICATIONS

- Certified Web Developer by Creativeo
- CISCO introduction to Cyper security Certification
- · ICDL Certification